(Love In Sync)
(Kim Myung Soo)
(Kang Min Ah)
(Love In Sync)
(All people, incidents, and backgrounds...)
(in this drama are fictitious and unrelated to reality.)
(Also, children and animals were filmed under production guidelines.)
This is the highlight of the awards show.
Soon, the actresses will vie for the spotlight...
in a fierce battle of the gowns, right here on the red carpet.
(32nd Korea Film Award)
In this bloody battle, dubbed the "War of Flowers,"
who will emerge as tonight's victor?
Darn it. A pound.
This darn pound.
I told you I was only having three pieces of kimbap yesterday.
So why'd you make me eat five? Why?
Because I was worried you'd collapse.
- A pound isn't even noticeable. - I can notice.
Right.
She's so intense.
How many shots are we doing today?
FYI, Han Yi Jin got 300, and Oh Soo Ah got 400.
Then obviously...
It'll be more, right? All right, let's do 600 then.
Add more contour.
Make it really alluring.
Wow.
Bravo.
Stunning, as always.
From any and every angle.
I am flawlessly beautiful.
You guys are so lucky.
- Yes? - Lucky how?
You get to gaze upon my beauty at every moment.
Why go to the Louvre?
Venus is standing right here.
- Am I wrong? - You're right.
- It's so true. - Absolutely.
It's so, so true.
It makes me so sad.
Why can I only see myself in a mirror?
It's so unfair. It's killing me.
We're going to be late.
- We should go. - I suppose. Let's go get my award.
Why?
You should've just beaten him half to death.
- What? - He made your life a living hell.
You have to pay him back for what he did.
What are you talking about...
What, are you afraid you'll lose?
- Are you chickening out? - No, I'm not.
Then what is it?
Now that it's time for revenge, do you feel sorry for that bastard?
- Crazy? Do you know what he did? - My point exactly.
That bastard is the reason you're in this pathetic state.
You dropped out of school like you were running for your life...
and now you're cooped up in your room, living every day in hell.
You have to make that bastard feel this shitty too.
An eye for an eye, a tooth for a tooth.
Get it?
Are you really sure this is okay?
I'm relieved he seems more energetic than before, but...
what if this leads to him doing something truly dangerous?
Our first priority is to save his life.
Seon Woo is suffering from depression, lethargy,
and suicidal thoughts due to relentless bullying.
What's the most effective way to restore his will to live?
Understanding and forgiving his abusers?
Or distorting and forgetting what happened?
Revenge.
For people who want to give up everything...
with full despair and rage,
a thirst for revenge can be...
a surprisingly powerful motivator to live.
Sir, I know exactly what you're worried about.
But...
you're aware of my skills and experience...
as a counsellor.
I promise I'll bring back the son you remember...
as quickly as possible.
Of course, you know what you're doing. I was worrying for nothing...
Since you're here, why don't you stay for a meal?
Our housekeeper is an excellent cook.
Thank you for the offer, but...
I have another appointment.
I'm sorry.
Yes, this is Cha Eun Hwan.
Yes.
Yes. Where did you say you were from?
You know our show, right? "Luckies on the Block."
It's a pretty famous show. All you have to do is make an appearance...
and your public recognition will skyrocket overnight.
Yes, I'm well aware,
but I have more than enough recognition as it is.
But it's TV. It's on a whole new level compared to word of mouth.
Well, I'm not really...
Hello?
- Excuse me. Excuse me, Counsellor. - Oh, yes.
I appreciate the offer,
but I'm afraid I'll have to pass.
("From Colleagues To Rivals, Han Yi Jin Versus Yu Ji An.")
("Who Will Be Awarded In The Best New Artist Award Tonight?")
Your jaw is going to fall off.
How many pieces of gum are you chewing?
What other choice do I have to reduce the puffiness?
You think just anyone can become a star?
This is all part of self-maintenance.
Don't you know what being a professional is?
Hey.
What is it? You keep sneaking glances at me...
like a puppy that needs to go out.
- What is it? - Well, before we leave,
the CEO called.
CEO Kim? What about him?
Well, I'm not sure how I should tell you this...
What is it?
Hey, before I tell you, can we agree on three things?
First, no getting mad.
Second, no yelling. And third, no cursing.
If you can promise me that, then I'll tell you.
I promise, okay?
So, you know...
What kind of bullshit is that?
(Yu Star)
Just answer the call.
What? Answer it so I can get chewed out?
It's better than getting cussed out to your face.
Getting yelled at over the phone is better, right?
You have an image to maintain as the CEO.
Darn, that's strangely persuasive.
(J.An Entertainment)
- Hey, Yu Star. What's up? - Why is the order so messed up?
Why am I scheduled before Han Yi Jin? Why?
Ji An.
Calm down and listen to me, okay?
The organisers set the schedule and just notified us.
What was I supposed to do?
So they told you to jump, and you asked how high?
Like some stray dog rolling over and showing its belly? Just like that?
Hey, does your mouth have to be so foul?
Do you think this is like changing the lineup...
for a girl group's music show?
This is a prestigious film festival in the country.
When they decide something,
how can the CEO of a small agency change it?
If I make a fuss trying to change it,
I'll get on the industry's bad side, you know?
Besides, people already say you're a...
There are already rampant rumours about you being rude,
so we don't need to add fuel to the fire.
- I'm just thinking of you. - CEO.
Can't you hear that sound?
Why? What sound?
The sound of my reputation taking a nosedive.
Don't you know what placement and order mean in this business?
Putting me before Han Yi Jin means that she's ranked higher than me.
And you want me to just accept that in front of everyone?
Are you insane?
Even as an idol, I was always in the center position.
Hey, so what? Things have changed now.
What has changed?
(Kim Jun Sik)
What I mean is...
that it's already been decided.
- Turn a blind eye this one time... - And?
You can't fix it. Is that it?
It's not that I can't...
I'm trying to say it's beyond my capabilities.
Fine.
- If you can't, then I will. - Do what?
Hey, hey, Ji An. Hey, Yu Star.
Don't do it, okay? Don't do anything, you hear? Hey, Ji An.
What kind of crazy stunt is she about to pull?
Ram into them.
- What? - I said, ram into them.
Ma'am, you're not serious, are you?
Right, you are serious.
Your performance in your latest film was wonderful.
I just love how vibrant your acting is.
It really feels like the character is alive.
That's only because I learned by watching you, ma'am.
Listen to how sweet you are.
Han Yi Jin.
I'm sorry, but we're going to have...
to ask you to switch places in the lineup.
No one was badly injured,
but they just have to make a quick stop at the hospital.
We apologise and ask for your understanding.
My today is our...
You're so beautiful.
- Please look this way. - That was Han Yi Jin...
who is cementing her place as a true actress.
Her outstanding acting also earned her a nomination...
for the Best New Artist Award.
Wow.
And Yu Ji An has finally made her grand entrance on the red carpet.
As always, she is absolutely stunning.
We heard she was in a car accident on the way here,
so we hope she's all right.
- Look over here, please. - Over here.
What is she doing? Why is she just standing there and not moving?
I'll go when you go.
Wow. It looks as though they're planning on walking in together.
Their friendship, which has lasted since their days in a girl group...
is truly making for a beautiful night.
What's this? An unwelcome reception?
I didn't think we were that close.
Just think of it as a little show for the public.
You're good at that, aren't you?
Please look over here.
Ji An, could you look to the right, please?
- Please look this way too. - Could you two give us a smile?
They're both nominated for the Best New Actress Award tonight.
Their friendship is strong, so whoever wins...
I'm sure they'll both be sincerely cheering for each other.
The best of friends and friendly rivals.
A relationship like that is truly enviable.
And speaking of nominees, here comes another one now, Kwon Hyun Jin.
- Gosh, it's freezing. - Welcome.
I'm hungry. Feed me. Food.
Oh, gosh. Look what the cat dragged in.
Feed me.
I'm so hungry. So hungry.
So cold.
Next, let's see the nomination of Music Awards.
Let's check out the first nominee.
Dude, you really ought to eat a proper meal every once in a while.
I wish I could.
But an hour of my time is far too valuable to waste on a single meal.
- You know what I charge per hour. - Oh, I'm well aware...
that you'd win a gold medal for being obnoxious.
- Hey... - Be quiet. I'm watching this.
You started it.
Now, let's move on to our next nomination.
Why is a guy who only watches porn watching an awards show?
Hey, my favourite star is up for the Best New Artist Award.
As a fan, I have to be part of this glorious moment.
- What are you talking about? Who? - Who do you think? Yu Ji An?
I was even the Fan Club President at one point.
You've had tons of "shes" like that.
If you think someone's even a little pretty,
you're signing up for their fan clubs right away.
Why do you always have to like...
Hey, what's wrong with my Ji An?
Oh, right. Because she's your crush's rival?
What crush? No, it's not like that.
- Hey, just go out with her already. - I said no.
Do you want me to sue you for spreading false rumours?
- It's really not true? - No.
That's ridiculous...
First, let's watch the nominations for the Best New Actress Award.
You're lying, right? A car accident?
The first nominee is...
Is your suspicious nature incurable?
How have you not been cured yet?
Her role was a murderer...
It's all thanks to your pathological lying.
You were like this when you were an idol too.
Whenever there was a gig you didn't want to do,
you'd whine that you were sick or tired.
And you'd just slip away.
Thanks to you, the rest of us suffered.
If you call that suffering, then I must have bled to death.
While you guys had just 1 gig and 1 practice,
I was sleeping four hours a day,
running from variety shows to events.
Thanks to that, our group got famous...
and I even split the money I worked myself to death with you.
That's why our fans called me the "charity angel,"
and you guys were the "parasites."
The next nominee is...
Because of those hateful comments,
Yu Ju was even hospitalized for depression.
Because of a critical mistake...
And as if that wasn't enough,
you selfishly left and our group disbanded.
That just means she was weak.
- What? Weak? - It amplified...
Let's get our facts straight.
Why is the group's disbandment my fault?
You're asking because you don't know?
As soon as you got popular,
- you ditched us and went solo. - That's why...
A group that disbands just because one member leaves...
Doesn't that just mean you guys were hopelessly incompetent?
In the past...
Why should I feel responsible or sorry for your incompetence?
In this competitive world.
- You're right. - It's really...
- That's true. - Whoever gets the award...
The fact that we were tossed aside as soon as you left...
must be because we were incompetent.
Okay, next up, we have the presentation...
- of the Best New Actress Award. - But...
- Presenting is last year's winner, - Aren't you curious?
- Park Hyo Jin. - About what?
Let's welcome her to the stage.
(Korea Film Award, Best New Actress Award)
- Now that the tables have turned, - Hello.
- who's the incompetent one? - I'm really grateful...
When we were idols, you were the amazing center...
and I was the pathetic nobody.
- But now that we're actors? - I think...
- Who's the center? - The 32nd Korea Film Awards.
- And who's the nobody? - The Best New Actress Award is...
going to Han Yi Jin for "I Was Wrong."
Congratulations.
Han Yi Jin played a role of Kim Seon Hwa,
a vicious character in "I Was Wrong,"
who betrays her loved ones.
With a delicate performance...
that captured Kim Seon Hwa's growth through her tears,
she was praised for doubling the character's charm.
Why Han Yi Jin and not me?
I...
I worked so hard.
I worked really, really hard.
Today, rather than the "throwing a fit" concept,
it seems she's going for the "frost in May" concept.
She's crying like a ghost from a folktale, full of deep resentment.
I thought maybe if she won the award,
I could use that chance while she's in a good mood...
to slip her the contract renewal.
But of course, Han Yi Jin had to be the one to win it.
- Wow, you were dreaming big, boss. - What?
Honestly, if she had won the Best New Artist Award today,
that would have been proof that the organisers were corrupt.
But based on tonight, it seems like a very fair awards ceremony.
I have total faith in them now.
As her manager, you should believe in and support...
your star no matter what.
I do. I totally support her.
But fairness... Well, that's a whole different matter, you know?
But really, should we be hanging around here?
Isn't it better to take off before we get caught in the fallout?
"Isn't it better?" That's informal, kid.
Don't you see it's raining out there?
You know she goes nuts if we leave her alone when it's raining.
Hey.
Let's wait for it to stop, then look for...
- a chance to bolt. Got it? - Okay.
Oh, you're out.
Are you okay?
I'm hungry.
Here we go again.
It's not much, but please enjoy.
- This is a ton of food. - Okay.
Are you really not going to eat?
You should just eat to your heart's content on a day like this.
Right, right, right.
I already didn't win the award. You want me to get fat too?
This is a feast for you two, so enjoy.
Okay.
Thanks. But seriously, how are we supposed to eat all this?
- I'm getting in shape. - Shut it.
Just listen while you eat.
I'm just really curious about something.
And I want you two to be honest.
You have to tell me the absolute truth.
- About what? - About what?
My acting...
Is it worse than Han Yi Jin's?
I just can't wrap my head around it.
The idea that I'm not as good as her?
However...
Crying in this situation is...
- what amateurs do. - Exactly.
So I'm going to analyse this like a professional.
Today's judging results.
Hey, what are you talking about? You're not worse than her.
It's all just luck. Pure luck.
- Awards are 80 percent luck anyway. - That's right.
Look, honestly, everyone has a different reaction to acting.
The whole idea of objectively judging something...
so subjective is a joke.
- Right? - Totally.
From my perspective, your acting was way better.
Oh, stop lying.
- I'm serious. - I'm serious.
No, don't be like that. I'm asking you to be completely honest.
It's the only way I'll be able to improve.
- It's true. - It's true.
If you two keep lying, I'm going to get seriously angry.
What? We're not lying.
Seriously...
Can I be honest?
So you were lying this whole time.
Go on.
Tell me what you really, honestly think.
Well...
Out of a sense of duty as your manager,
I analysed your acting.
It's not that you're a bad actor, but...
how should I put this? It lacks soul.
Soul?
Like, you laugh when you're told to laugh...
and cry when you're told to cry.
I can't feel any understanding or immersion in the character.
Is that what it looked like to you?
- Look who's the critic. - No, I wouldn't go that far.
But then I thought about why that might be.
I think it might be because you lack empathy.
Lack of empathy?
Well, you don't really consider other people's perspectives.
You tend to be a bit selfish and self-centered, don't you?
And what is acting?
It's about expressing another person's life and emotions.
That's hard for someone like you. Don't you think?
You can have the rest.
Eat up.
Oh, man.
Hey, it's a good thing the rain stopped.
If it hadn't, you and I...
would have died a glorious death by food torture here today.
- Sir. - Yes?
Do you know a good place for antacids?
- Antacids? - Yes.
- Hey, Do Hoon. - Yes?
Run, run, run.
Running is best for indigestion, you fool. Run.
- That won't work. - Run, run. Let's go.
Why are you doing this to me?
What are you talking about?
What am I to you, Mom?
Ye Rin.
All you ever think about is my sister.
What about me? I've spent my life worrying about you...
because I felt sorry for you.
Don't I get hurt too?
- Am I made of steel? - And what is acting?
It's about expressing another person's life and emotions.
That's hard for someone like you.
I'll try. Ready, action.
Even Mom...
The kids' juice that even moms want.
A nutritious after-school snack, Juicy Juicy.
Cut. That was excellent.
Ji An.
Why did you do that?
What do you care if she forgets her lines?
But they said you're supposed to help a friend in need.
Who said that? What kind of idiot?
Her mistake was your opportunity.
Why? Why would you do something so stupid, why?
Look at me.
Do you want to go back to the orphanage?
I don't want to live apart from you anymore, Ji An.
For that to happen...
You have to listen to me, right?
Ji An.
You must never...
be the kind of person who needs to be nice to others.
You need to be someone who doesn't have to be good.
If you behave like that,
the world will be nice to you...
and treat you well.
Understand?
A gift.
Thank you so much for earlier.
Get lost. I'm telling you to get out of my sight.
That's not it.
That emotion right there...
What about it?
The stage directions say to shout in rage.
But what kind of emotion do you think that is?
She tells the man she loves to get lost,
but deep down, she wants him to stay and hold her.
That's the desperate feeling underneath it all.
It's not just about screaming your head off.
(Not Just Screaming)
You don't understand what that feels like, do you?
That's why your acting isn't improving.
Let's take a short break.
They're dissing you, right?
I knew you were on the association's bad side, but to do it so openly...
How can people be this petty? Seriously.
The jealousy of lesser men is just something the great have to endure.
Let them. It's actually kind of amusing.
Today's the day for free consults, right?
- Lee Young Ji's scheduled at 2pm. - Oh, yes.
Sir.
Should we send a bouquet to Yi Jin?
She's a VIP at our clinic. We should at least congratulate her.
Best New Artist Award.
(Cha Eun Hwan)
(Counsellor Cha Eun Hwan)
I enjoyed the awards ceremony yesterday.
Congrats on the Best New Artist Award.
Thank you.
I wanted to hear you congratulate me more than anyone.
I'll treat you to something big to celebrate.
When are you free?
You're here? One moment, please.
What? You come here?
I switched.
The director kept begging me to come so she could show off her skills.
You've really made it.
The director here only works with the best of the best.
Did you cry yesterday?
Me? Why?
Because you were upset that I won the award instead of you?
I wasn't upset.
My face is just puffy. I ate ramen.
You? The girl who won't even swallow her own spit...
after 6pm to avoid gaining weight?
It was just one of those days.
A day where you just want to let yourself go.
Yesterday was that day.
- So you were upset. - I said I wasn't.
Ma'am, they said the car is waiting and to please come down.
You're Mi Jeong, right?
Hi, it's good to see you.
Long time no see.
You work for her?
You must have your hands full.
You should ask for some extra contouring today.
Your face is as round as the moon.
Unbelievable.
Is my face really that puffy? Darn.
Hey. I almost lost it watching the awards ceremony yesterday.
About what?
Whether it's class, looks, or popularity,
how could Han Yi Jin win over you? Does that make any sense?
I guess the judges thought differently.
Look at how naive you are.
There's a reason for everything, you know.
A reason? What reason?
Director Yoon, who was one of the judges, and Han Yi Jin...
They have a thing going on.
Hey.
Do you know Yi Jin?
Yes?
I wouldn't say I know her...
But I do know her.
So shut up and do your job.
Did you see Yu Ji An's outfit?
She's wearing Erbeni. Why am I wearing Arden?
Well... Erbeni doesn't sponsor just anyone.
What makes me...
just anyone?
I don't care what it takes.
Get Erbeni to sponsor me tomorrow. Got it?
Yes.
Yes, I'll be in touch.
We just heard from Director Moon.
Director Moon?
The Moon Gyeong Sik?
Yes.
("Casting Moon Gyeong Sik's New Film")
("Who Will Be Next Cinderella?")
So, Director Moon is pushing for Han Yi Jin,
but the production company is against it.
She lacks star power, I guess.
The production company is pushing for our Yu Ji An,
but Director Moon is against it.
She lacks acting skills, I guess.
A showdown between star power and acting skills.
But why isn't our Ji An's acting improving?
If she stars in Director Moon's film,
her acting career will be set for life.
That's why, sir...
I've come across some incredible information.
(Cha Eun Hwan, Mental Counsellor)
So this guy's really that good?
What is he, some Bodhisattva?
No, he's a psychological counsellor.
They say he's amazing at reading people.
He not only treats trauma and compulsions...
but he also draws out emotions hidden in the subconscious.
They say he even helps actors improve their skills.
He's the talk of the town in this industry.
- Yes. - But will Ji An go for it?
The catharsis from imaginary revenge...
can sometimes be a form of self-healing.
Looks like my counselling has been quite helpful.
Your depression, anxiety, and suicidal ideation scores...
are much lower than before.
Your social worker told me you found a job.
Just cleaning buildings.
Congratulations. You don't have to come in for sessions as often.
I think once a month should be enough.
Okay.
Then we're all set.
But, Doctor.
I shouldn't actually turn that fantasy into reality, right?
Young Ji.
Imaginary revenge is just a counselling technique...
I know.
I was just saying.
Right.
Then we're all set.
Oh, not again.
Mr. Lee.
Mr. Lee?
Just a second.
Yes, this is Cha Eun Hwan.
Yes, where are...
You're booking a session for who?
Honestly, about the incident five years ago...
He wasn't the only one doing wrong.
No, that's not it.
Honestly, the fact that you're still...
so shaken up because of him... It's frustrating.
In Kyung, desperately and sorrowfully, like you're wailing.
(Director Kim Jin Uk)
You...
I... I love you so much.
(Actor Jeong Da Eun)
I...
(Director Kim Jin Uk)
- I love you. How could you... - Ji An.
The mood is a little flat.
Can we try it with a little more emotion?
Let's go again. Cue.
(Director Kim Jin Uk)
Director.
Let's take a quick break. I'm not feeling my best right now...
(Director Kim Jin Uk)
- Let's take a ten-minute break. - Okay.
What? Therapy?
What, do you think I'm some kind of psychopath?
Hey, Yu Star, calm down. Hey.
You're Gen Z. How can you have such an old-fashioned view of therapy?
Even normal people go to therapy these days.
Whatever. I don't want to.
Hey, I'm telling you, it's not just any therapy, you know?
It's apparently amazing at bringing out emotions...
that people have suppressed in their subconscious.
Actors who have had sessions with him say...
their acting improved dramatically.
- I still don't want to. - Why?
(J.An Entertainment)
My private life is already public.
Do I have to expose my subconscious too?
What if the therapist starts spreading rumours about me?
There's such a thing as professional ethics. You think he'd do that?
If he did, there'd be rumours everywhere by now.
Listen.
You should not trust people.
You're so naive.
Forget it. I said no, so I'm leaving.
Where do you think you're going?
Hey, I heard Yi Jin went there.
- What? - Her acting has gotten much better.
It all adds up.
(J.An Entertainment)
You're sure this will be kept confidential?
Yes, this is Cha Eun Hwan.
You're booking a session for who?
You know the actress, Yu Ji An? I'd like to book a session for her.
Of course, I can assume it's completely confidential?
(Counsellor Cha Eun Hwan)
Right. It's just a job.
I'll just focus on that.
Yes, come in.
Can I really go home for the day?
Yes, you can head out.
Just who is this VIP client...
that you're sending me home early? I'm a little offended.
Come on, you know our center's claim to fame.
Absolute...
privacy.
Well, getting to leave early is nice, but...
Be careful with this.
Don't forget and get locked in again...
then don't call me crying like last time.
Yes, I'll keep that in mind.
- Go on. - Okay.
What's with this rundown building?
It looks more like a fortune teller's place.
They said it's a therapy center. Let's give it a chance.
Fine. Let's give it a chance.
What? Are you coming with me?
Are you going to go in alone?
If every Tom, Dick, and Harry knows about it, how is that private?
Stay here.
Tom, Dick, and Harry?
(Tok Tok Mental Care)
(Notice: Building Power Outage, December 18)
(Due to electrical work in the building,)
(temporary power failures may occur.)
Done looking at my face? Should we go in now?
Please, come in.
(New Client Intake Form)
(Average)
(Degrees, Certifications, Awards)
I thought it was an exaggeration,
but I guess the rumours about you being good are true.
Well...
I wouldn't know, but that's what I hear.
That I'm quite skilled.
So this is what it feels like. When people call me arrogant.
Come over here and pick a card.
You're very defensive.
Am I?
Your intake form is almost entirely gray.
Always in the middle, between "no" and "yes."
Neither black nor white.
Only non-committal choices.
I don't know. I don't think of myself as defensive.
Just now, you picked the first card without a second thought.
Making an immediate choice to maintain a sense of control...
is a classic trait of someone with strong defence mechanisms.
During the selection process,
they're afraid of revealing their inner selves.
What was your childhood like?
Why do you want to know?
This is your session, Yu Ji An.
A person's disposition is mostly shaped...
by their childhood experiences.
Especially their relationship with their parents.
How was yours?
Was it a good one?
Well...
Not particularly...
good...
or bad.
It was average.
Yu Ji An.
The client needs to be honest...
for us to have an effective session.
You feel intense fear when you're alone on a rainy day.
It's also accompanied by claustrophobia...
which you don't normally experience.
Just like the weather today.
It's not that serious.
A fear that responds to a specific condition...
is a conditioned trigger response. A form of trauma.
In your childhood,
did you ever experience a major accident?
Excuse me a moment.
Yes, we're closed for the day.
What? A power failure?
Open the door. I said, open the door. Please, just open the door.
Claustrophobia.
Open the door.
Ji An. Ji An, are you okay? Can you hear me?
- Ji An. - Please open the door. Open it.
Please, open the door.
(Tok Tok Mental Care)
Ji An, you need to step away from the door, okay?
Open the door...
Please... Please help me.
(Tok Tok Mental Care)
Please, open the door.
Ji An, are you okay?
I can't breathe.
Look at me. Look into my eyes.
Okay, now just do what I do. All right?
Breathe in. One, two.
Breathe out. Three, four.
Good. You're doing great. One more time.
Hey, kid, snap out of it. Hey, kid.
I promise I'll save you.
I'm sorry.
Mister.
Sorry...